hello guys back to you
i'm rohan your guide for this session
we already have learned to afford a
great pitch
moving on let's explore objection
handling in this video
so how do we do that by going through
some case scenarios
shall we begin scenario one
customer says the rate offered by public
sector banks
are less than icici bank
let's speculate the response shall we
sir i agree that psus offer roi
closer to what we provide but also the
gold rates per gram offered by icici
bank
are very attractive not just that our
good customer service
and streamlined processes ensure a lower
tax
for dispersal of the loan
scenario two customer says
leading nbfcs offer one percent interest
rate per month on product
icici bank has higher roi
so here the customer is informed about
the nbfc's interest rate
and has a thought that our roi is higher
so
what can be the fit response let's hear
it
sir when compared to most of the nbfcs
icici bank's offerings are at par
and competitive we offer attractive
ltv and rate per gram in fact
i would request you to consider the
total amount including interest
penalties and other charges that you
will have to pay
in nbfc offering at icici bank with no
emi gold loan
there is no worry of penalties on
missing or delaying
installments hence the total amount
payable
does not exceed unnecessarily scenario
3.
customer states other private banks have
low rate of interest
and processing fees
this is the tricky part while private
banks offer
lower roi they also charge other fees
and installments in advance
be very cautious while explaining this
part to them
sir definitely you might have had done
research
about it at your end but have you also
noticed the assessment
or the appraisal fees and installments
asked in advance
in these banks because we at icicf bank
do not seek appraisal charges or
installments of
any kind you as a customer can optimally
utilize the loan amount
for the desired purpose and pay the
entire interest and principal
at the end of the loan tenure scenario
four
customer states product emi offered by
other banks
is more suitable with installments and
will not burden with paying of
entire amount in one go sir
icici bank gold loan has the facility of
making
part payments that to any number of
times within the tenure
as per the availability of funds you can
make payments
at your leisure this will reduce the
interest amount
that you will pay at the time of
maturity however
the jewelry will be released only on
account closure
in addition to this with no emi product
you do not have to worry about huge
penalties charged
on missed or delayed emis
you have mastered the skills of perfect
sales
let's know what it has in store for you
in the next video